André Madureira e Souza Soalheiro de Moraes

Senior System Analyst

A passionate System analyst focused on development and people with more than 9 years off experience. I'm currently working as a Sr System Analyst developing and architecting secured payment transactions in Java(Spring Boot, Ant, JPA) using microservices context, ReactJS for the tools and working as well as a Leader of 4 developers and 1 Scrum Master.



andremadureira1993@gmail.com 🔀

+55-19-98891-5675

Rua dos Tocaúnas, 43, Campinas, Brazil 👂

linkedin.com/in/andremssmoraes in

andre.m.s.s.m 🕲

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior System Analyst & Interaction Leader

HST Card Technology

03/2020 - Present Security payments solution

Campinas- Brazil

Achievements/Tasks

- FullStack Developer: Working as a fullstack developer in the Digital Payments Solutions. The solution is composed by Mobile(Wallet), Front(Transaction Controls) and Backend(Integrations and Cryptograph) Solutions that works in the entire flow of the digital payments. Stack: Java(Spring Boot, ANT, Maven, Open-Api, API-First Design, Junit), ReactJS, Docker, Jenkins, RabbitMQ, ShellScript, Postgresql, MongoDB, Elastik, Swagger, Wildfly and Crypto algorithm.
- Interaction Leader: Leader of a team with 4 developers and 1 Scrum Master.
- Solutions Architect: Specifications of payments integrations solutions. Stack: DrawIO and WebSequence.
- Scrum Master: Worked part time as a Scrum Master.
- Project Leader: Responsible for the continuous delivery and evolutions of some products.

System Analyst Icaro Technologies

05/2017 - 03/2020 Digital Transformations Campinas - Brazil

Achievements/Tasks

- Software Engineer: Worked as a contractor for Motorola Solutions(Chicago) team developing integrations with the Command Central system to APIs(REST and Soap). Stacks: Javascript, Typescript, Java, Azure, Azure Service Bus, Gitlab, Docker, Kubernetes, REST, CID/CD, SOAP and NSIS.
- Fullstack Developer: Development of a Ícaro Tech internal product named Flex Forward used to generate reports for customers needs. Stacks: ReactJS, Java, Javascript, Docker and Gitlab.
- IBM Maximo: Development of customizations in the tool.
 Stacks: Java, Wildfly, IBM Maximo and Gitlab.
- BMC Remedy Developer: Worked with ITSM to develop flows in BMC Remedy. Stacks: BMC Remedy and Java

SKILLS



EDUCATION

Architecture off Distributed Software Master Degree

PUC Minas

03/2020 - Present

Courses

- Architecture Principles
- Backend And Microservices Architecture
- Architecture Refinement
- IOT
- Cloud

- Front End Architecture
- Nodejs Architecture
- .NET Architecture
- DevOps, CI/CD

Computer Science Degree UNIP

01/2014 - 12/2017

System Technician CEMEP

01/2009 - 12/2011

Courses

 Programming languages course: Java, VB, C#, C++

Paulínia - SP

EAD

WORK EXPERIENCE

System Technician CPqD

12/2012 - 05/2017

Campinas - SP

A Brazilian company of technological innovations

Achievements/Tasks

- Backend Developer: Creation of process automation for excel operations using VBA Macro as programming language.
- Customer Support: Focus point for the HSBC in the TEM project.

System TechnicianMaster Certificações

02/2012 - 10/2012

Campinas - SP

Certifying Anatel

Achievements/Tasks

- Website support: Used a internal tool to update website content, as new, products and etc.
- IT Support: Worked as an internal team support for everything related to laptops and networks issue.

Intern

Institutio IBTA

12/2011 - 02/2012

Paulínia - SP

A Brazilian clinic specialized in terap

Achievements/Tasks

 Website Development: Development of a website used as a blog, constructed using Html, CSS and Javascript.

CERTIFICATES

Scrum Foundation Professional Certificate (07/2020 - Present)

Credential ID 4859219 -

https://www.linkedin.com/company/certiprof/

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Spanish

Professional Working Proficiency

French Elementary Proficiency

Portuguese

Native or Bilingual Proficiency